<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Haptic Feedback Survey App</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="home_section">
        Open the survey on another device.\n\nRead the instructions on the first page of the survey.
        \n\nWear headphones.
        \n\nMake sure to be concentrated on the task without distractions.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, swipe from right to left to start.
    </string>
    <string name="button_section">
        This is the button section that shows 4 buttons with different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first button gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the \"button 1\" and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to \"button 2\" and so on until \"button 4\".
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.
    </string>
    <string name="slider_section">
        This is the slider section that shows 4 sliders with different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first slider gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the first slider and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to the second one and so on until the last one.
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.
   </string>
    <string name="checkbox_section">
        This is the checkbox section that shows 4 checkboxes with different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first one gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the first checkbox by selecting and deselecting it
        and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to the second one and so on until the last one.
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.
   </string>
    <string name="toggle_section">
        This is the toggle section that shows 4 toggles with different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first one gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the first toggle by turning it on and off
        and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to the second one and so on until the last one.
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.</string>
    <string name="spinner_section">
        This is the spinner section that shows 4 spinners with 3 elements each and different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first spinner gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \nThe already selected elements if selected again give no feedback.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the first spinner by selecting items
        and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to the second one and so on until the last one.
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.</string>
    <string name="rating_section">
        This is the rating section that shows 4 rating bars with different vibration patterns.
        \nThe first one gives no feedback and it is not part of the survey.
        \n\nWhen you feel ready, start to interact with the first rating bar and answer the questions related to it.
        \nThen, move to the second one and so on until the last one.
        \nWhen you have finished to answer the questions related to this section, move to the next page by swiping from right to left.
    </string>
    <string name="end_section">You have done!
    \nRemember to submit the survey!</string>
    <string name="greetings">Thank you very much for you time, \nyour answers will be helpful!</string>
    <string name="credits">
        Alessandro Iop 〉 iop@kth.se
        \nFederico Landorno 〉 landorno@kth.se
        \nDH2670 Haptics, Tactile and Tangible Interaction
        \nInteractive Media Technology
        \nKTH, Stockholm, Sweden
    </string>

</resources>
